[
  {
    "question": "The property used to change the text color in CSS is _______.",
    "answer": "color"
  },
  {
    "question": "The property used to change the background color in CSS is _______.",
    "answer": "background-color"
  },
  {
    "question": "The property used to set the size of the text in CSS is _______.",
    "answer": "font-size"
  },
  {
    "question": "The CSS property used to make text bold is _______.",
    "answer": "font-weight"
  },
  {
    "question": "The property used to align text in CSS is _______.",
    "answer": "text-align"
  },
  {
    "question": "The CSS property used to control the spacing between lines of text is _______.",
    "answer": "line-height"
  },
  {
    "question": "The property used to set the outer space of an element in CSS is _______.",
    "answer": "margin"
  },
  {
    "question": "The property used to set the inner space of an element in CSS is _______.",
    "answer": "padding"
  },
  {
    "question": "The property used to set the border style in CSS is _______.",
    "answer": "border"
  },
  {
    "question": "The CSS property used to hide an element from a webpage is _______.",
    "answer": "display:none"
  }
]
